yuuguu.com 2017-06-12

# Yuuguu | Privacy policy. How Yuuguu keeps your private information private

**NOTICE:** The Yuuguu service will be closing on 31st May. Contact [support@yuuguu.com](mailto:support@yuuguu.com) for other available products. 

## Yuuguu Service Privacy policy

**1\. Personal information**

  1. (a) _Account activity_. You need a Yuuguu Account to access the Yuuguu downloadable client. Yuuguu asks for some personal information when you create a Yuuguu Account, including your email address and a password, which is used to protect your account from unauthorized access. A Yuuguu Account allows you to access many of our services that require registration. 

When you use the Yuuguu downloadable client, we may record information about your usage, such as when you use Yuuguu, the size of your contact list and the contacts you communicate with, and the frequency and size of data transfers. Information displayed or clicked on in the Yuuguu interface (including UI elements, settings, and other information) is also recorded. 

You do not need a Yuuguu Account to access the Yuuguu web based service. Yuuguu asks for some personal information when you use the web based service, including your email address, a password, a screen name and a 6 digit PIN code. 

When you use the Yuuguu web based service we may record information about your usage, such as when you use Yuuguu, the people you communicate with and the frequency and size of data transfers, Information displayed or clicked on in the Yuuguu web based service interface (including UI elements, settings and other information) is also recorded. 

  2. (b) _Content_. We will store the contents of text chats. These text chats are only stored when they all participants in the chat use the Yuuguu downloadable client. 
  3. (c) _Payment details_. We do not store any of your financial details (eg credit card number). All our payment processing is performed by SagePay.

## Yuuguu Website Privacy policy

Yuuguu is dedicated to the fundamentals of protecting your privacy. Personal information may be collected from our visitors on a voluntary basis. This may include name, e-mail address, address and telephone number.

The personal information retained may be used by us to process an enquiry and/or for communication of service related information.

The personal information retained may also be used for the communication of marketing related information with Yuuguu Account owners. Yuuguu Account owners can request that such communication be stopped by sending an email with the heading 'Unsubscribe' to [support@yuuguu.com](mailto:support@yuuguu.com).

The personal information retained may be used for the communication of marketing related information with users of the Yuuguu web based services provided that they have agreed to opt in to such use.

We don't disclose personal information to 3rd parties for any purpose. Additionally, our web servers use cookies to track unique (non-identifiable) visitors to our website. This information is aggregated to measure the number of visits, average time spent on the site, pages viewed, etc. Yuuguu uses this information to measure the use of our site and to improve our content and services. Yuuguu does everything it can to keep all information from our online visitors secure against unauthorized access and use.

All information is protected by our security measures, which are reviewed regularly.
